

賴 宛蒂 / 溫蒂



WANTI LAI / WENDY

eizagreen

ABOUT

I am a web designer based in Taipei. January 16, 1985 was born in Taichung. I love to design clean and solve the problems. I am a logical thinker, imaginative creator, effective communicator and always willing to try new things. Because of past work experience, for the branding, seo and marketing operations are also full of good cognition. With a passion for creating delightful digital products, having the opportunity to do so is what keeps me motivated each and every day.

我是個網頁設計師,1985/01/16出生於台中。喜愛乾淨的設計和解決問題,對於數位領域有極大的熱情。我有邏輯性的思考能力,充滿創意的想像力,有效率的溝通能力,並有面對新事物的學習力。有鑒於過去的工作經驗,對於品牌、SEO和行銷操作也有很好的認知。能有機會參與創造更多好的數位產品設計,是我每天努力學習前進的動力來源。

SKILLS

WEB DESIGN

RESPONSIVE DESIGN SASS HTML5 CSS ANIMATIONS

熟悉網頁設計流程,對於如何操作RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN更是相當有心得,當然也會使用SASS的寫法。偶爾會玩一下CSSANIMATIONS。

UI/UX DESIGN

WIREFRAMING Mockup

有能力執行從網頁架構端到完成品的整體視覺規劃,對於切版和與後端技術人員的溝通都有十足的信心,並且知道合理的技術支援範圍,創造出符合良好使用者體驗的互動介面。

DEVELOPMENT

JQUERY GITHUB

不害怕找臭蟲,可以寫寫基礎的 JAVASCRIPT及JQUERY,喜歡整 理及使用乾淨的語法。樂於與團 隊合作,希望能開始愛上(與大 家一起)使用GITHUB的樂趣。

EXPERIENCE

2013/5~2015/5

HEARST MAGAZINES TAIWAN 台灣赫斯特媒體股份有限公司 NEW MEDIA & WEBSITE, HEAD OF VISUAL 新媒體暨網站視覺統籌

2011/6~2013/4

MEGAIS DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY CO., LTD 邁格數位有限公司 CREATIVE DESIGNER 資深網頁設計師

E D U C A T I O N

2003/9~2007/6

VISUAL COMMUNICATION DESIGN OF NTUA 台灣藝術大學 視覺傳達設計系 學士